(Sheldon:)Cluck-cluck-cluck.
(Amy:)Sheldon, look at me.
(Amy:)I think it's time
(Amy:)to face the fact
(Amy:)that Leonard is the nucleus
of your social group.
(Amy:)Where he goes, the group goes.
(Sheldon:)Leonard the nucleus?
(Sheldon:)That makes no sense.
(Sheldon:)I'm the whimsical elf
(Sheldon:)that everyone looks to
for a good time.
(Amy:)I'm not saying
that you're not fun.
(Amy:)You're the most fun person
I know.
(Penny:)A lot of people think
I'm fun to be around.
(Amy:)Don't be needy, bestie.
(Amy:)That's probably part
of what chased Leonard away.
(Amy:)What I am saying, Sheldon,
(Amy:)is that your group
is Leonard-centric.
(Amy:)If it were a town,
it would be Leonardville.
(Amy:)If it were an Islamic nation,
Leonardstan.
(Amy:)If it were the birthplace
of motion pictures,
(Amy:)we'd all be singing
"Hooray for Leonardwood."
(Penny:)Ooh, I got one.
(Penny:)If you guys were a band,
(Penny:)you'd be called Leonard
and the Leonards.
(Amy:)So needy.